iboats.com 2009-06-19

# About iboats- Privacy Policies

**This is a web site owned by iboats, inc.**  
  
Our postal address is:

_iboats, inc._  
170 West Election Road.  
Suite 100  
Draper, UT 84020  
USA

We can be reached via e-mail by [clicking here](http://www.iboats.com/contactus.html), or you can reach us by telephone at **800-869-1686** or **801-571-0071**.

  * Overall Privacy Policy
  * Detailed Privacy Policy Regarding Information Collected On Our Site
  * Our Commitment To Data Security
  * Opt-Out Procedures
  * Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
  * How To Contact Us

_Overall Privacy Policy_

Your privacy is one of our primary concerns. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the options available to you to govern how your information is collected and used. We make this policy available on our homepage and at every point where personal identifiable information may be requested. Our dedication to your privacy means: 

  1. We will NEVER sell, rent, or share your your e-mail address.
  2. The information we collect is used only within our own organization to improve our services and to better service our client's areas of interest.
  3. If you elect to provide us with additional information (by filling out forms, etc.), we will collect it and only use it to improve our product offerings and services to you.
  4. On occasion we may market specials and offers from trusted third party vendors, we will only share your personal information that you authorize us to provide should you accept one of these third party offers (for example, your name and mailing address for a free magazine subscription).
  5. Please be aware that we host sites for a number of dealers and other clients, who may have privacy policies that differ from ours. Please see their individual privacy policies for more information regarding their sites' policies.

_Detailed Privacy Policy Information Collected_

We collect only the domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our web pages, aggregate information on which pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumers, such as survey information and/or site registrations. 

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web pages, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web sites, and used by us to contact consumers for our own marketing purposes or our trusted partners when authorized by the consumer. 

_Our Commitment To Data Security_

Please be assured that we have put in place appropriate security measures and procedures to protect you against the loss, misuse, and alteration of any information we receive from you. In all areas where your information is collected, iboats uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions ([more info](http://www.thawte.com/html/RETAIL/ssl/index.html)). 

_Opt-Out Procedures_

Each of our opt-in e-mailed newsletters has its own clearly defined removal procedure. Please review the information included in each newsletter for removal instructions. If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by writing to us at the above address. 

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contacts from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line. Please provide us with your correct phone number. 

_Our Commitment To Children's Privacy_

Protecting the privacy of children is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18 years of age, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18 years of age. 

_How To Contact Us_

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at the phone number listed at the top of this page, or send us an email at the email address listed at the top of this page.
